hotelrooms.com 2003-06-26

# Hotel Rooms Privacy Policy

HotelRooms.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html) for information about our site's security for online transactions. **

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This Privacy Policy covers HotelRooms' treatment of personally identifiable information that HotelRooms collects when you are on the HotelRooms site, and when you use HotelRooms' services. This policy also covers HotelRooms' treatment of any personally identifiable information that HotelRooms' business partners share with HotelRooms.

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that HotelRooms does not own or control, or to people that HotelRooms does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * HotelRooms collects personally identifiable information when you register for a HotelRooms account.

  * When you register with HotelRooms, we ask for your name, email address, and address.  Once you register with HotelRooms and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  * HotelRooms also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, and the page you requested.

  * HotelRooms uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * HotelRooms will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

  * HotelRooms will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

    * We have your consent to share the information;

    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;

    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of HotelRooms to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; 

**Cookies**  

  * HotelRooms may set and access HotelRooms cookies on your computer.

  * HotelRooms allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to HotelRooms' cookies.

**Security**  

  * Your HotelRooms Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

  * In certain areas HotelRooms uses industry-standard [SSL-encryption](http://www.hotelrooms.com/pegs/security.htm) to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * HotelRooms may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

  * This site, www.Hotelrooms.com, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>
